♪ In the
not-too-distant future ♪
♪ Next Sunday, A.D. ♪
♪ There was a guy named Joel ♪
♪ Not too different
from you or me ♪
♪ He worked at
Gizmonic Institute ♪
♪ Just another face
in a red jumpsuit ♪
♪ He did a good job
cleaning up the place ♪
♪ But his bosses didn't like him
so they shot him into space ♪
♪ We'll send him cheesy movies ♪
♪ The worst we can find ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ Then we'll monitor his mind ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Now keep in mind
Joel can't control ♪
♪ Where the movies
begin or end ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Because he used
those special parts ♪
♪ To make his robot friends ♪
♪ Robot roll call ♪
♪ Cambot ♪
- Pan left.
♪ Gypsy ♪
- Hi, girl.
♪ Tom Servo ♪
- What a cool guy.
♪ Crow ♪
- What a wise-cracker.
♪ If you're wondering how
he eats and breathes ♪
♪ And other science facts ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Then repeat to yourself
it's just a show ♪
♪ I should really just relax ♪
♪ Called Mystery
Science Theater 3000 ♪
(whistling)
- Come on, Crow, let's go!
- Yeah, yeah, just a sec, Tom.
Hi, everyone!
Welcome to the Satellite
of Love, I'm Crow T. Robot,
and this here's Tom Servo.
- Howdy.
- We're retrofitting each
other with belly buttons.
- Yup, turns out our
compere Joel Robinson
completely overlooked
belly buttons.
- So we're just
doin' it ourselves.
- Yep.
- Oh, and there's
a good chance we're
doing something
incredibly stupid!
- Again!
- Yeah!
(laughing)
- But once it's done, Joel
can't do anything about it.
This isn't gonna
hurt, is it, Crow?
- Nah, Mariette Hartley had
two navels in Genesis II.
- Okay, oh, be sure to
put some lint in it, too.
- Sure!
- All right?
- Okay.
- Let's do it!
(laughing)
- Good gravy, what
are you guys doing?!
- Well, hi, Joel.
We're givin' each
other belly buttons.
- You can't do that.
- Oh, okay.
We weren't that sure.
- Why, Joel, why?
Why can't you give me the gift
of one simple belly button?
Look at me, Joel!
I, who have none.
- Yeah, Joel, we don't
wanna feel weird around
the other guys in
the locker room.
- Please?
- Okay.
(cheering)
- Hey, if this works out,
can I have an Adam's apple?
(metal boring)
(laughing)
Oh yeah!
This was definitely a mistake.
Drillin' holes in
our midsections.
Look at that poor schmo,
man, there but for
the grace of god go I.
- Quiet!
I'm contemplating
my Bondo'd navel.
- Oh, Quisp and
Quake are calling.
(laughing)
- That Fannie Flagg is a hoot.
Durwood, it's them.
Let's talk baseball.
Better yet, let's talk
baseball sponsors.
Better yet, let's
just talk. (laughs)
Ah, baseball, the
great American pastime.
But how can we, as
evil scientists,
hope to dilute or even destroy
this great summertime event?
Frank?
- Oh boy,
this is gonna be dark.
- Thanks.
Our Invention Exchange
is based, roughly,
on the popular baseball
promotion night.
You know, Hat
Night, Sock Night--
- Tunnel of Chili Night.
- Right.
But we've made it
evil and hurtful,
you know, like we like to do.
(laughing)
So we've re-written
the baseball season
with some unsavory,
and in some cases,
downright dangerous
cross-promotional giveaways.
- For the season opener we have
Colorless Odorless
Toxic Gas Night.
(coughing)
- [Clayton] This
Knothole Day special,
the first 10,000 lucky
kids get slide whistles.
- [Frank] Oh boy!
- And the second lucky 10,000
kids get real brass knuckles.
Then, the first 10,000
lucky kids become unlucky.
(moaning)
- Oh! (laughs)
This symbol here represents
the lovable, huggable,
San Diego Chicken,
which must mean
it just happens to
be Crossbow Night.
(mimics a crossbow firing)
- Frank, right on, give me five!
(moaning)
(laughs) You are righteous.
Then there's the
promotional tie-in.
The beauty of this concept is
is that it hurts the company
supplying the product
as well as the fan themselves.
- Dow Corning presents
Fiberglass Insulation Night.
- [Clayton] Park Davis
presents Used Syringe Night.
- [Frank] Tires Plus presents
the Peppermint Schnapps,
Tire Iron Double-Hitter.
(laughing)
- Well, that's about
as evil as it gets,
don't you think, Joel?
(slide whistling)
- Oh, sure, sirs, that's
real evil, of course it is.
Well, our Invention
Exchange this week
is based on some foot fashions
and some clever wordplay.
Tom?
- Thanks, Joel.
Say, ever notice how the
trendy shoes Doc Martens
and the name of the popular
mad cartoonist Don Martin
almost sound the same?
Well, we did.
- Right!
And our Take a Walk on
the Wild Side department
has converted the command table
to a high fashion
walkway to present:
- Doc Martens for
Don Martin, Joel?
- Yes, yes.
Don Martin, the maddest
of the mad cartoonists,
has a real flair for
drawing funny footwear.
- And Doc Martens,
British shoe importer,
also has a real flair for making
and selling funny footwear.
- So I say combine 'em!
- What do you think,
Chester Bester Tester?
- How about Poopie
Night? (laughs)
- Poopie.
Your movie this week, Joel,
is a little piece of dreck
called The Girl in Lovers Lane.
Poopie Night, Frank.
- Hey, come on, that's funny.
- I'm not saying it isn't funny,
what, you gonna give kids poop?
- Well, I--
- Movie sign!
(laughing)
- Nice shoes.
Burlington Northern presents
a film by Casey Jones.
- How's that, Mr. Jarmusch?
- Wait, we just
want to pants you,
we've never pantsed
a hobo before!
- He doesn't understand the
concept of hopping a freight.
- Ollie ollie friggin' oxenfree.
- Sir, we just want
to punch your ticket!
- Calvin Klein jeans.
- Damn Jehovah's Witnesses!
- Richie Brockelman,
the lost episodes.
- Hey, my trusty library card.
- I heard a wallet over there.
- Scotty, beam me out of here.
- Hey, he rolled himself.
- Like wallet, like son?
- Stamp all butts dead out.
- Well, at least he's a donor.
- Hey, I think we're losin'
our significance here,
we better do some crimes, man,
or be written right
out of the script.
- He does look like an
easy target for thugs.
Hell, I'd like to beat him up.
- Sneak, Von Ryan, sneak!
- Oh, you know, this happened
on Thomas the Tank
Engine one time.
- Okay, you join our discussion
salon or you're dead.
- I'll hold him, you
search his pockets.
- You do the voice,
I'll move the jaw.
- He's clean.
- You're crazy, I saw
the roll he was packing.
- I haven't got any money.
- You're lyin'.
- Damn student loan association.
- I tell you, he was loaded!
He must've ditched it somewhere.
- Now you've done it.
- I knew this guy was
carryin' a fat roll.
- And some bagels, too.
- Yeah, yeah, sure.
Get yourself a pair of glasses.
- All that work for nothing.
- Don't cheapen the moment.
- Come on.
- Kidnapped, the Frank
Sinatra Jr. story.
- (gasps) It's Jesus.
Or maybe not.
- In Oxfords?
- Well...
- (grunts) Oh, good heft.
- Hey guys, look
what I just found.
- I'm gonna put him in
my room and pose him.
- And thus, the
passenger train is born.
(cool music)
(screaming)
- Whoa.
Almost got me there.
♪ The Girl in Lovers Lane ♪
♪ With Jack Elam
not Jack LaLanne ♪
♪ Not LaLanne ♪
♪ And lots of actors ♪
♪ There's no time to name ♪
♪ A screenplay by Jo
Heims that's pretty lame ♪
♪ Pretty lame ♪
♪ The entire crew ♪
♪ Feels a sense of shame ♪
♪ Shame ♪
♪ If only they had ♪
♪ Half a brain ♪
♪ They could attain
a measure of fame ♪
♪ From a film like Shane ♪
♪ But no, to their disdain ♪
♪ The Girl in Lovers Lane ♪
(whip cracking)
- The Girl in Lovers Lane.
- Hey, wake up, Snowball,
the credits are over.
- Hey, I'm in here, do ya mind?
- You got a weak jaw, boy.
They hardly touched ya.
- I know, I'm kinda a fem.
My friends call me Wormy.
- Oh, wait a minute,
where's my Certs?
I meet a new hobo and
I have bad breath!
- Christina's World.
- You've got somethin'
that belongs to me.
- Well now, I guess maybe we
got something to talk about.
- Well, that'll make
the time go fast.
- I want that wallet.
- Is that okay?
- You want to take it from me?
- Nah, you'd probably
just clobber me
and I'll wake up six
hours later, then.
- I watched you out there, kid.
You were scared.
Real scared.
Why, you're scared right now.
- Really quite scared.
- Tell you what.
- Don't hit me!
- I'll give you car fare home.
- I'm not goin' home.
- Well, where ya headed?
- That's my business.
- But you don't seem
to understand, kid,
you're outta business.
- You're under bankruptcy
protection from the court.
- You had a hundred bucks here,
how come you're
hoppin' freights?
- It's kinda hard
to hop a plane.
- Well, you aren't used
to travelin' this way.
This is something new to you.
You don't even know how
to handle yourself yet.
- I got separated from
my band trip, okay?
- Meaning what?
- Meaning you don't know how
to hang on to what's yours.
If I give this back to you,
somebody else will just
take it away again.
- Good idea, you'd better hang
on to my clothes then, too.
- What's your name, kid?
- Sex Poodle, oh.
- Danny.
Danny Winslow.
- Bix Dugan.
- Big Stupid?
- Mr. Stupid, can I
have my wallet back now?
- War-torn Wisconsin.
- Wow, you got me a wallet,
and I just lost mine!
- If you'd said you
stole it, I'da kept it.
- How does that make you feel?
- Well, you better get
some sleep, Danny boy.
- I can't sleep now,
I'm too excited.
- I think maybe you
got a long way to go.
- And I'm gonna take you there.
- Hey, I call the
top bunk. (laughs)
- Hey, are we bound for glory
right now, Mr. Big Stupid?
- Rail, rail against the dying
of the light, rail. (laughs)
You were incredible.
- Bix?
- Can I have a glass of water?
- Are ya asleep?
- Yeah.
- I'm thinking.
- Can we snuggle?
- Don't, you'll weaken the team.
- I wrote a poem about you
while you were sleeping.
- Where you going, Bix?
- Back to sleep.
- I'm serious, wake
up and talk to me.
Where ya headed?
- This is getting weird.
- Wherever this train's
headed, I ain't particular.
- Should we call ahead
and make reservations?
- That's what I thought.
I've got an idea.
- Toaster pastries!
- Congratulations.
- Uh, Bix, don't laugh
at my footie pajamas
when I put 'em on, okay?
- All right.
- Hop on.
- What do you want
to talk about?
- Well, I was thinking about
changing the part in my hair.
- I was just thinking, since
you don't care where you go
just so long as you keep moving,
why can't we travel together?
- I've killed a bunch of
drifters, and you could be next.
- Well, for one thing, you
got a hundred bucks, kid.
And I don't know whether
you know it or not,
but a conventional vagrant
don't make much money.
- Well, the money will
be my part of the deal.
- You'll bring a sense of style.
- I, I'd just like to
have someone to go with.
- And I'll give you $10
every time you don't hit me.
- It's your loot, man.
I guess we're stuck
with each other.
- Dear diary, I think I'm
finally becoming a real vagrant.
Big Stupid says
he's gonna teach me
the ins and outs of drifting.
- At my age, I
gotta be a mother.
- Hey, this boxcar's enormous,
would you move, Danny?
- Uh, camera three
get off the track.
Camera three, oh dear god!
(screaming)
(fun music)
- I woke up and you
were there, I hate that.
- What's the matter?
- Seven minutes late, raccoon
on the tracks at Brixton.
- Could be nothin', they're
probably stoppin' for water.
- Is that bad, when
they stop for water?
Do you want me to get
you some water, Bix?
Is water a good--
- Just shut up, Danny.
- Oh.
- Hold me.
- Oh, it's just as I
dreamed it would be.
- Looks like we're
about a mile from town.
Better get off here.
- (laughs) Never mind.
- Why don't we just take
the train all the way in?
- Sure, all the way
in and right to jail.
Or did you buy a ticket
for this joyride?
She's slowin' down, come on.
- Mr. Big Stupid, catch me.
- Is this right?
Am I walkin' with ya right?
- I'll always remember you,
boxcar number 1837562093.
Bye-bye.
- I'd really like
to freshen up now.
- Gee, I thought Vegas
would be bigger and shinier.
- Get off the road, ya drifters!
- Like father, like bum?
Think about it, won't you?
- Is that a girl, my
lord, in a flatbed Ford,
slowin' down to take
a look at, oh, no.
- Hey, I want you to take
this kid for me, will ya?
- Hey, can we stop for
biscuits and gravy, Big?
- I think I sat on your keys.
- What town we comin' to?
- Funkytown.
- Sherman, nice little town.
- I'll say!
No ifs, ands, or buts.
- Two Moon Junction.
- Laura Petrie, no!
- Laura Petrie, yes.
- Actually, guys,
it's Millie Helper.
- That's real nice, ma'am,
but you're still under arrest.
- See ya later, Carrie.
- You're so very.
- Hey, train'll be in soon.
- Oh, it's just another freight.
- It'll still be in soon.
- Oh, Peggy, not another one.
- Just a half one.
- You'll get fat.
- Johnny isn't complaining.
- Johnny's pretty wild.
You've been seeing
a lot of him lately.
- Well, he's better
than nothing.
- You haven't tried nothing.
- You haven't been seeing
anybody, you never do.
- Oh, I can't talk to
boys the way you do.
- That's silly, Carrie.
Besides, who has to talk?
- Oh, I get it. (laughs)
- Uh-oh, look who
just walked in,
Sherman's answer to
the brainless wonder.
- Hey, it's Abe Lincoln.
- My pa left a list of
things for you to get, Jesse.
- Some lice shampoo and a comb?
- You understand what
you're to do now?
- I don't think you're
gettin' through, honey.
Try drawin' pictures.
- Hey, what did I say?
- Jesse, I'm talking to you.
- I know, I just
like to look at ya.
- Oh wow, maybe I should
leave you two lovebirds alone.
- No.
- Supposed to go
down to the store
and get your pa some
supplies, is that right?
- Yes, that's right.
- As a young man,
Garrison Keillor was
shunned by his friends.
- Thank you, Jesse.
(growling)
- I wish that I
was Jesse's girl.
- Smells like Derby
canned tamales.
- Honey, you're trembling.
- Am I?
I don't ever want to
be alone with him,
just the thought of it--
- Oh, stop it, Carrie,
for goodness sakes.
He's as harmless as a pup.
- Yeah, Cujo.
- Everybody knows it.
The poor idiot likes
you, that's all.
- It's the way you're dressed,
who wouldn't leer at you?
- What you need is a
man, honey, I know.
You'll see, one'll come
along, they always do.
- (laughs) That's our Midge!
♪ Green eyed lady, sexy lady ♪
- I've had enough of you
two, now get out, out, out!
- Big, should I have not put
my head in the driver's lap?
Was that wrong?
- Look out, Sherman,
here we come!
- Shut up, Danny.
- Oh.
- Ever been here before?
- Small towns are all the same,
you seen one, you seen 'em all.
- Well, the zoning's different.
- I'm hungry, let's
get something to eat.
- That's a good idea.
- You're catchin' on, kid, that
was very insightful of you.
- We're hungry, but
I thought of it.
You know, you think that
could be my new job, Bix?
Decidin' when to eat?
- Shut up, Danny.
- You won't tell your old
man I was late, will ya?
- No, of course not, but--
- But what?
- You shouldn't have brought
her in here with you.
- Oh, what's the harm?
- You know how Pa
feels about her,
he's told you time and again
not to let Sadie in here.
- How is he gonna know,
unless you tell him?
Let me worry about it.
- Hey Mel, kiss my grits!
- Tom, don't ever
say that again.
- Sorry.
- Okay, what'll it be?
- Well first, a little respect,
we ain't bummin' a meal.
- [Pete] Oh, money men, huh?
Well now ain't that interestin'.
You're gonna have to excuse
the looks of this place,
we ain't used to caterin'
to the carriage trade.
- Ouch.
- Well do you think
you could get back here
with a menu before
the food goes bad?
- Food's bad already.
- The girl will
wait on you, bud.
- What is this, the Sad Cafe?
- Go on up there and
wait on those clowns.
- All right.
(circus music)
- Hi, I'm Midge,
can I start you out
with some grilled mahi-mahi
in a grapefruit cream sauce?
- Don't fall in
love with us, baby,
we'll hurt you every time.
- Well, have you made
up your minds yet?
- Have I ever.
(mimicking alarms)
- Dive, dive!
- Oh, you mean the order?
Well I'll have scrambled
eggs and coffee.
- Okay, you want juice, salad,
roll, grapefruit
half, or pudding?
- Rosie, the early years.
- I didn't think life
could get any worse.
I'm gonna go turn on the gas.
- I've got a feeling
you're spending
the rest of our
money right here.
- You're not ready
for quits yet, Danny.
- Well now, what I got
in mind, Danny boy,
shouldn't cost me.
- We're drifters, you?
(door opening)
- Oh, you have
your food already.
How'd you do that?
- Should I use a fork, Bix?
- Say, you're new in
town, ain't ya, honey?
- Yeah.
- The open road is
our home, ma'am.
- Well, come on over,
Sadie wants to talk to you.
- Suddenly this is Rain.
- Sit down, baby.
- I like the welcome wagon here.
- Now, tell me all
about yourself.
- Well, I don't have any bones,
I'm just cartilage, and...
- Well, can I tempt
you with some desert?
- Sorry about that earlier
sexism thing there.
- Is she wipin' his lap?
- No.
- Hey, you missed a spot.
What's your name, honey?
- Carrie.
- I'm so very.
- [Carrie] Carrie Anders.
- Bet you have a
lot of boyfriends,
pretty girl like you.
- No, I'm saving myself
for the right oily drifter.
- Condiment man,
get your condiments.
- Jesse, put that--
- We hit a wrinkle in time!
- Fine.
- The delivery man
always rings twice.
- That's an unusual odor.
- Is he one of them?
- One of what?
- One of your boyfriends.
- Oh no, that's Jesse.
He does odd jobs around town.
- Very odd jobs.
- You know, you're a
beautiful girl, Carrie.
- You're so very.
- I bet you got a yellow dress.
- And yellow eyes.
- With ruffles on
it or somethin'.
- Rumples?
- You're making fun of me.
- No.
Hey, why don't you put
that dress on tonight?
You and me'll go for a
walk, maybe take in a movie.
- I'd like that.
- Will you have to be there?
- But I don't know your name.
- Bix.
- And I'm Danny!
- What time do you get off?
- Eight.
- Can I pick you up here?
- Yeah, I live under the
counter, so I'll be right here.
- Daddy, there's
a drifter outside.
- Danny.
- Get outta my underwear.
- That's a nice name.
Where ya stayin', kid?
- In a boxcar on the
edge of town, ma'am.
- Save it, honey.
There ain't no business here.
- Now, wait a minute--
- Besides, he's only a kid,
he wouldn't
appreciate it anyway.
- Listen, you--
- Cut it out, Bix.
- It's nice to meet someone
with manners for a change.
- So now your day's complete.
- Let's have more
breakfast, Danny.
- Now I don't wanna
catch you messin' around
with my friend here,
I got no manners.
Pay the check, tiger.
- Grr, I'm gonna pay
the check now, grr.
- Come on, pay it.
- Okay, what's 10% of 79 cents?
- Why'd she keep
calling me John?
- Oh, bye-bye.
Hey, Cambot, could you
do that music again?
("What a Pleasant Journey"
by Michael J. Nelson)
Yeah, good.
Hello, ladies and gentlemen,
my name is Joel Robinson
and there's nothin' that
sets my heart a-wanderin'
like the sound of a
train whistle, Tom?
- The call to the open road,
the urge to chuck it all
and hop a freight train
is one of the most romantic
notions of the century, Crow?
- That's why we've decided
to write our own train songs.
We hope it brings out the
same travelin' vagabond,
everywhere I hang my hat
is home spirit in you,
Joel, if you will?
- Thank you, Crow T. Guthrie.
♪ I hear that train comin',
comin' 'round the hill ♪
♪ I hope that is my train,
I'd better check my schedule ♪
♪ Oops that was the
train to Appleton ♪
♪ But it's goin'
to Circle Pines ♪
(whistling)
- Yee-haw!
♪ And I've got about
20 minutes to kill ♪
♪ It's a good thing I
brought some magazines ♪
Tom?
♪ Been ridin' on this old train,
been riding it all night ♪
♪ I think I'll go to the club
car and get myself a bite ♪
♪ Mm this tuna melt sammich
really tastes quite nice ♪
♪ Oh it's got sesame
seeds in the bun ♪
♪ Plus it comes with
coleslaw and a pickle ♪
♪ And I must say it's
reasonably priced ♪
Crow!
♪ The 5:15 from Duluth,
oh my it just derailed ♪
♪ The toxic waste is spillin',
the conductor's been impaled ♪
♪ A benzine cloud has risen ♪
♪ And the whole town's
starting to cough ♪
(rhythmic coughing)
♪ Within a matter of days all
of our skin will fall off ♪
- I'm gonna pick one now.
- Okay.
You know, Cambot, could ya?
You know, guys,
I get the feeling
we're not really cut out to
do train songs after all.
I really think that, being
who we are in space and all,
we're a lot better suited
at singing about being
♪ In cars ♪
(fun music)
- I don't know about this.
- Please, Pa, we're
just going for a walk.
- I know, but after all,
he's a stranger in town.
What do you know about him?
He's a drifter, here one
minute, gone the next.
- He's wearing a stomach sock.
- I don't want anything
to happen to you, honey.
I'm kinda fond of you.
- Pa, he's the first boy I've
seen that I wanna go out with.
- And I'm approaching
menopause, for Pete's sake.
- Well, he's kind
of easy to talk to.
- Your grandmother's easy to
talk to, take a walk with her.
- Please?
It's important to me.
- It's hard to tell
if he combs his hair
forwards or backwards.
- All right, honey.
- He's got six fingers!
- It's Larry and
Balki's apartment!
Oh.
- I like watching
you shave, Big.
- She's not that kind of girl.
- Oh, grow up, you didn't fall
for that shy routine, did ya?
- You're not gonna pick my,
your nose again, are ya?
- It's only seven, still
got an hour to kill.
- Maybe I'll kill you.
- Hey, let's check the
action in this town, huh?
- [Danny] Right.
- Uh, that's the closet, Big.
- Let's drop by Barton
Fink's for a drink.
- Oh, and Danny,
about all that loot
you've got padding your pocket.
- What about it?
- Well, me with
all my experience,
don't you think I oughta
kinda look after it?
- No, I'll hold onto it.
- What's the matter, don't an
honest face count for nothin'?
- No response needed, come on.
- Nobody trusts nobody anymore.
- You got your key?
- Come on, Big, we've been
by the appliance store
three times now, there's
nothing going on.
- How's your game, Danny boy?
- I never played pool.
- You never played pool?
Didn't they teach
you nothin' at home?
- Anything.
- Come on, follow me.
- Hey, it's the
Catholic teen center.
- Are we going to
hustle these men, Big?
- Change for a 50, please.
- The color of Danny.
- Did his head just
turn into a big sucker?
- What are you tryin'
to do, buy the place?
- Just break the 50, huh?
- That was a lot of
money back in those days,
he probably could've
bought the place.
- How do you want it?
- Two 20's, a five, four
ones and some change.
- Wait, make that three 20's.
- Listen, why don't I
just save you the trouble
and give these guys the money?
- Two 20's, a five, one,
two, three, four, change.
You got it, buddy.
- You got pull-tabs here?
- Oh, hi.
- Well, rack 'em up
and call the ambulance.
- So, this is pool, huh?
- I cut my teeth
on these babies.
- I'm sorry.
- Hey, you know,
we never knew how
to work this thing before.
- Watch him close, you
guys, he's an expert.
- Hey, there's Squiggy.
- Never mind them,
go ahead and play.
- I am Xenon, play me.
- Never mind us.
Let's prove how good
a champ you are.
- Is this the way
it's gonna be, man?
- Yes, no, pass.
- Friend, you're
carrying a lot of money.
- Yes we are, thank
you very much.
- Now why don't
you use some of it
to prove how good you are?
- Let's go get a snow cone.
- Well I ain't a gambler.
Me and my friend here are
just killing a little time.
So why don't you take your
kindergarten and blow?
- Oof, my tummicological region.
- Sure.
We'll cut out.
- Well, that was awkward.
- Hey, do you guys know anything
about that prostitute lady?
No?
(whistling)
- Street's got awful dark,
be careful when you
leave here, huh?
- Thanks, safe home to you too.
- The tension in
the air is palpable.
- Why do you drive
people away, Big Stupid?
- Do they mean what
I think they mean?
- That it's dark outside?
- What's that, Danny boy?
- That they'll be waiting
for us outside, is that it?
- That's the message I got.
- Is it okay that
I wet my pants?
- Well, what do we do about it?
- Well I think maybe
we should just run!
- Bix?
- Bix, yoo-hoo!
- Well, let me see,
if you wanna look
on the dark side,
we get killed and
they get our loot.
- And, being in a
state of mortal sin,
we go straight to hell.
- On the bright side,
we keep our loot,
but we get killed anyway.
- I think I see where
you're goin' with this.
- Any way you look
at it, Danny boy,
looks like we're gonna
get our heads bashed in.
- Well, is there another
mentor around here, like you?
- Just readin' Cathy,
leave me out of it.
- Bix--
- Will you change me?
- Why do we have to fight
if we don't want to?
- Testosterone.
- Why can't we just--
- Love.
- Because that's the
way things are, kid.
- Uh-huh, uh-huh.
- I told ya once, it ain't
easy to hold onto what's yours.
Sometimes you
gotta fight for it.
- Well, we better not
keep them waiting.
- Yeah, they might
get angry and hit us.
- I guess.
- Well, let's get
down to business.
- Okay.
- There's four of them--
- And one of you.
- Come here.
- Now what I'm gonna do,
see, is I'm gonna kill you
and strap you around
my body for armor.
- Four of them and two of us.
That just don't come out right.
- What's so funny?
- Any way you look at it,
we're gonna get killed.
- I don't wanna be a
hobo, I wanna be a nurse.
(door opening)
- Uh, I forgot my comb,
comb over here, I forgot it.
- Uh, which one of
you is Big Stupid?
- George says to tell
you he'll make a deal.
- I'll give ya $5 if you've got
a hard-boiled egg in your purse.
- Hand over the wallet
nice and peaceful
and you can walk outta here
the same way you came in.
- Well now that
don't make sense.
- I thought it
didn't sound right.
- If we give you our wallet,
we go out of here flat broke,
and man, that ain't
the way we came in.
- Is that your answer, then?
- That's it, sonny.
- Okay, all right, well
I'll just, let, let's,
I'm gonna let Jerry know and
I'll, I'll come back to you.
Okay.
- I think he likes me.
- Can I have change
for a 50, what a dummy.
- Come on.
- (whistles) Here, boy.
Come on, Danny, there you go.
- Sir, can you change
this back into a 50?
- Well, I didn't expect to spend
the whole 50 bucks in
there, we're flat broke now.
- They got away,
that was brilliant!
- Certainly not worth
mugging us for, um, 75 cents!
- The dark side of Mayberry.
- Yeah, if Andy were here,
he'd outwit them with
some homespun wisdom.
- I feel sorry for
the unfortunate
mugger who mugged us.
- Hey, um, what's the downside
of running again, Big?
- Really good show tonight
with Topo Gigio, really good.
- See this alley?
- It's where you're gonna die.
- Pay attention.
- Ow.
- Do you see this alley?
- Yeah.
- Well this is where
it'll be, then.
Now you do like I say and
we'll save a few teeth.
- Remember folks, a backhand
will knock him cold for hours.
- Hey, it's got all the
furnishings from their boxcar.
What, in the, go, without,
geeze, stop it, jerk.
(fun music)
(dangerous jazz music)
- I'll get a tricorder
reading, captain.
(meowing)
- Frankie Valley and the Four
Seasons of the Apocalypse.
- I'll give 'em a manicure
they'll never forget.
(humming)
- Oh, this is the alley
where Fonzie was introduced.
Eh.
- Sit on it.
Plop plop, fist fist,
oh what a fight it is.
- Where's he going?
- I don't know, I can't see him.
- What are you
waitin' for, Danny?
- Don't hurt me, I have
this glass jaw thingy.
- Danny likes ya, mister.
- Oh, look out, look out, I
dropped my thing, okay I got it.
- Spartacus.
- Frodo is in one
of those barrels.
- Well that smacks of
Tolkeinism. (laughs)
- Watch out for the recycling.
- He's tryin' to
uncomfortable him to death.
- Oh, he looks good in a choker.
- Oh Danny, please help,
help, Danny, help, Danny.
- Must save Spock.
- What's that little
guy doin' in there?
- Crosby, Stills, Nash, and
Young have creative differences.
- Long may you punch.
It's Donny Most and Joel
Grey in a fight to the death.
- You guys need
anything in there?
- The cross and the switchblade.
- Mom!
- What were you doin'
down there, kid?
- Come on, kid, let's
get back to the room
and get you fixed up.
- How about your date?
- Oh, forget it, it
ain't that important.
- Wait a sec, I'm
just gonna pop this.
- Man, have you
got a lot to learn.
Hold still.
Now the idea is to keep your
face away from his fist,
not put it out there
where he can find it.
- Guess I'm not
much of a fighter.
- Well what are you whisperin'
for, it ain't no secret.
- How about that guy
I groined in the knee?
- You know, first
thing in the morning
we're gonna have to
get some new clothes.
If the sheriff sees
us in these rags,
he'll throw us in
jail for vagrancy.
- Is that Constitutional?
- Bix?
- Yeah?
- Any more of
those Fi-bars left?
- I was scared.
If you hadn't been
there, I would've run.
I almost did anyway.
- What a wuss.
- Well we're all
scared sometimes, kid.
When you're in a spot like
tonight, you have two choices.
You can stay and face
it and be afraid,
or you can run and be ashamed.
It's up to you which is
easiest to live with.
- I'll take the latter.
- That ain't too bad,
a plastic surgeon would
fix you up in no time.
Take a look.
- So am I supposed to look
like a Picasso painting?
- My dad would
never believe this.
- You two didn't get
along so good, huh?
- Well sure, he's
quite a guy, a lawyer.
- Well level with me, kid,
what's this back alley trip for?
- Well you may as well know,
I'm the prince from
Lichtenstein, Big.
- He said they were
getting a divorce.
- Dad made it clear
it was my fault.
- Just like that, he said it.
As though 19 years had
been a waste of time.
- Oh, you can see
the string, look.
- Well so you cut
out, you ran away.
- How do you choose
between two people who have
always seemed like one to you?
- I've never had that problem,
I wouldn't know what to tell ya.
- You're on your own
on this one, Danny.
- You're crowding
me into a corner.
Between my--
- Danny, this isn't the answer.
- My dad's man-to-man talks,
I couldn't think straight.
I had to get away from them.
- This is not your
induction physical, Danny.
- Maybe without them pushing,
I can work things
out for myself.
- I'm gonna take some money
out of the till for booze,
okay, honey?
- We made over $5 today,
that's a lot for these days.
- At nine o'clock,
business goes under.
(screaming)
- You said your dad's a lawyer,
does he make good money?
- He's always been able to
give me whatever I wanted,
within reason.
- Tell me another story, Big.
- I guess you'd
say we're as close
as a guy and his dad can be.
- Big, was it somethin'
I said in the fight?
- What's funny now?
- Sounds like my old man,
we were real close too.
Took me everywhere he went.
I knew every beer joint in
town by the time I was eight.
- That's somebody's
ideal childhood.
- He gave me a lot
of things, too.
Mostly his fist to my face.
- Did he swing it or just
place it there gently?
- Well, I'm gonna go
continue the cycle.
- Oh, I know these kind of
guys, honey, he's a drifter.
They never stay put very long.
He might've left
town last night.
(door opening)
- Here's the lunch rush.
- Shall I?
- No, Pa, I'll take the order.
- Back off, dad, he's mine.
- Hi, Carrie.
- Hi.
- How ya doin'.
- What are you going to have?
- I don't know, what do you got?
- Anger and resentment.
- I waited for you last night.
- Oh yeah, hm.
- Yeah.
- Well. (coughs)
- Something came up
outta nowhere and--
- I had a trans-species
experience last night.
- Landed all over his face.
- (laughs) Oh.
- Hey, no kiddin'
Carrie, I'm sorry.
Let's make it for
tonight, what do you say?
Same time?
- All right, tonight.
- Sucker.
- Hi.
- Can you imagine?
- What?
- Two hours I waited
for him last night.
- For who, what are
you talking about?
- Johnny, who else?
Two hours I wait and he
doesn't even show up.
Honestly, Carrie,
sometimes I don't even...
- Ixnay, Ellie May.
- I did it again, Big.
- Hello there.
- Hi, right back at ya.
- Peggy, this is
Bix and this is...
- This is Danny.
- Hi.
- You're kinda cute for a boy.
What happened to your face?
- What happened to
my face, Big Stupid?
- Oh he cut himself, shaving.
- And the moment collapses.
- You got a dime?
- Sure.
- I got 5,000 dimes.
- Follow me.
- Do you like Aqualung?
(relaxing music)
♪ Leather coat ♪
- You aren't mad about
last night, are ya?
- No.
- Good.
- You can walk over me anytime.
- Hey, don't forget
that yellow dress,
the one with the ruffles.
- Oh, and bring some
french fries, too.
- [Bix] Might even
take you dancing.
- Honest?
- Sure.
You got a portable radio?
- Gee, thanks.
- Good, bring it along.
- I still don't approve.
- Hey, who is that
character back there?
He keeps staring at me.
- Oh, Lester Flatt.
- Oh, that's my father.
- Oh, look at the time,
I'm due in Omaha at five.
- Come on, Danny.
See you later.
(fun music)
- So basically the plan is
to get him to ask for change
for the pinball machine,
then threaten him, and then
we beat the snot out of him,
like in the movie, right?
- Well, yeah, guess
that's it in a nutshell.
- That's beautiful, Tom!
- Thank you.
- But what if he
doesn't fall for it?
- Are you kidding?
He's like an overgrown child,
he's practically got rube
sewn into the back
of his underwear.
He's the poster child for
naivete, oh, shh, here he comes.
- Oh, hi bros, hey, my
old pinball machine.
- Yeah, wanna play?
- No, what else is goin' on?
- Nothing, Joel, not a thing.
We used our tricorders
to scan the SOL
for entertainment potential,
and the pinball machine
is the only thing that
even moved the meter.
- Well, you guys know best.
- (laughs) Poor dope.
- What's that?
- I said, "Do you
need any quarters?"
- You know, actually I
don't have any money,
let's just forget it.
- I'll give you
$50, need change?
- Crow, this doesn't
have any connection
to that weird beating scene
in today's film, does it?
- (scoffs) No!
I mean, sheesh, I can't
believe, geeze, Joel, I mean,
what would make you think that?
It's just that, geez, I mean--
- Yeah, right, like,
like hey Servo,
let's drag the pinball
machine on deck
and get Joel to ask
for change for his 50
and then hogpile him
by a bunch of crates
we set up to look like
the alley, yeah right.
Do you believe this guy?
- Believe this?
- Well, if it's all
right with you then,
I'll just borrow
one of your quarters
and play a game here, okay?
- No, of course, go ahead.
- That's right, duh, what
do you think it's there for?
(pinball noises)
- Uh, Joel?
- Yeah?
- You're not gonna take that $50
and come into our mock alley set
and let us hogpile you and
snag on you and stuff, are ya?
- Uh, no.
- Okay, I'll be right back.
(whispering)
- [Servo] Really?
- Joel?
- Yeah, honey?
- You're absolutely sure?
- Yeah.
- Okay, well, then
we're just going
to have to hogpile you here!
Servo, let's get him!
(screaming)
(alarm blaring)
- We got movie sign!
(screaming)
- Sorry, we had to
use the Mr. Ed set.
- What's wrong?
What'd I do now?
Women.
- You brought your tackle
box, no wonder I'm upset.
- So, this is Bass Lake, huh?
- My dress, it's blue.
I don't have a yellow dress.
- I tried to make it yellow
with my mind, but I got tired.
- And there isn't a
ruffle on it anywhere.
- (groans) I'm outta here.
- It's the best dress I've got.
- Third inning here
and Don Drysdale
is playing the game of his life.
- Come on, sit down here.
- Come on, move it,
haven't got all day!
(humming romantic music)
- Oh, feels like swollen glands.
- Move in.
- Well, I think we've found
our girl in lovers lane.
- Pa doesn't know very
much about girls' clothes.
- There's so much you
could say to that.
- You got a boyfriend,
somebody special?
- I thought you
were gonna be him.
- I don't know any boys, really.
I mean really know them.
- You know, her neck looks like
Randy Johnson's from
the Seattle Mariners.
- I don't get it.
- Yeah, me neither.
What?
- I love the rings they make
when they hit the water.
- Yeah, rings, right. (burbles)
- That rings thing
really bugs me.
- It'll be you,
me, and the moon.
You wear a necktie
so I'll know you.
- Oh, this is a great date,
I always wanted to
be nuzzled by a hobo.
- You smell like hashbrowns.
- Don't you dare mark me.
- Where the heck did your
lips go, oh, there we go.
- Remember, make the tongue
the reward, not the rule.
- Oh, forgive me for
responding to you.
- So when a man says
no, he means yes, right?
- Well...
- You know why I
brought you out here?
- To get to my father?
- Do you have any idea?
- For my tater tot
hot dish recipe?
To talk about hockey?
- No, you wouldn't.
- 'Cause you like shoes?
- Come on, kid,
I'll take you home.
- Okay.
- Sorry about being warm,
tender, and accommodating.
- Just a little dart from
the Coca-Cola company.
- Is Pa still here?
- In the back.
- He's makin' that
special sauce.
- Well, if it isn't
little Danny's mother.
I don't think the kid'll
need a mother anymore.
I think maybe tonight
he becomes a man.
- Yeah, how'd you
figure that out?
- Sadie was in here earlier.
- Said somethin'
about a bar mitzvah.
- Ain't she kinda
robbin' the cradle?
- He ain't in no
cradle tonight, friend.
- The meatloaf's good!
- Where'd she take him?
You hear me, where'd
she take him?
- What's this all about?
- This guy's nuts, Cal.
- Well what's going on here?
- This bum set my friend
up with that Sadie dame
and now he can't
remember where she lives.
- Sadie, how many times,
she lives around the
corner at 933 Elm Street.
- Third bedroom on the
left, pink lingerie hangin'.
- Pete, you're through.
No more excuses, just get out.
- You'll never serve
lunch in this town again.
- That's the last
time I hire a pimp.
(door slamming)
- Bill Haley!
- No.
(laughs) You know what?
Just found out this
place is a brothel!
Can you believe it?
- Well, I'll have
what he's having.
- It's Unforgiven
meets Making the Grade.
(humming seductively)
- Hey, Edie Brickell's in there.
- Now why is she
singing the theme
to the Six Million Dollar Man?
- I don't think that it's--
- It's a good show.
- What I wouldn't give to
be Mr. Bubble right now.
(laughing)
- Well what's your problem?
- Sorry, wrong room.
- Melanie Griffith?
- Are you waiting for a bus?
- I, said, well...
- Get the heck out of here.
Hey, wait a second.
- Bring mommy a beer.
- I'll be right out.
- Why did they have a
bathtub in the sitting room?
- Well, turn your back.
- Done.
- Now, what did I
come in here for?
Danny who? (laughs)
- Now that really appeals
to prurient interests.
- Naked floor.
- Well hello there, tassel feet.
- Joel, when I grow up
I want to be a drifter.
- How does that
towel stay in place?
- Nice shirt.
- Are you in the wrong room now?
- I've never been in a
righter room in my life!
- I don't know.
- If this room is wrong,
I don't wanna be right.
- You know what?
The problem is that she looks
like Kurt Russell
in Tango and Cash.
- Yeah, that takes away from it.
- Do you know now?
- Do you take Mastercard?
- I don't know what room I'm in.
- This hooker is just
prostituting herself.
- You know, bein'
with a hooker's just
too much of a commitment
for him, he can't handle it.
- Well, I,
I'll see you on the way out.
Ow!
- I'll just check
behind this green door.
- Hey, hello?
Missus prostitute?
- Danny?
Hey, she's got a skunk costume.
- It sounds like Eubie
Blake's in the next room.
- Sir, there's no late
seating until intermission.
- This is getting
into a weird area.
- Cindy Brady all grown up!
- Hey, a coupon for
the Frisco Melt.
- [Bix] Now, Sadie girl.
We both know you
ain't that expensive.
- Oh, you got me.
- Come on, put all that
green back where it belongs.
- Line, what, what's my line?
- Well now I'm just not
gettin' through to you, am I?
Tell you what, take
five out for yourself.
- 'Cause that's just
what you're worth.
- It'll cover the cheap booze
you used to get him drunk.
Sadie, I hate hittin' dames.
- Oh man, there's so much
not to like about this guy.
- Owie, stingy.
- You know, back in those days,
five bucks was a lot of money.
- What's a hundred minus five?
- Is this your falsie?
- Talk about dippin'
into the till.
- Didn't your mother
teach you any better?
Maybe you ain't dishonest,
maybe you're just illiterate.
Now you look real close.
See, a two and an O
side-by-side like that
make 20, Sadie girl, not five.
- She's a prostitute, you
can't really shame her, okay?
- Ain't you ashamed?
♪ Tears fall like rain ♪
- Cocktail?
- Sadie, don't.
- You know, why do all prostitutes
dress like Joan Blondell?
- Oh, he just broke Danny.
- You know, Danny should
come with his own tote.
- You know, once again,
Big has saved Danny
from a heterosexual experience.
- I'll just reschedule
at the front desk.
- Come here, buddy,
let's get you a nice,
honest, fresh hooker.
- Oh, Danny, you're killin' me.
- Ah, they're at the
Shady Rest Hotel.
- I got a stummyache, Big.
- Oh, he's gonna put
Danny down for a nap.
- Little nappy.
Yeah.
- Read me Stinky
Cheese Head Man, okay?
- Come back to bed, honey.
- You know, this guy's life
would've been a lot simpler
if he woulda just lost
his wallet and gone home?
- Yep, yeah, pretty much.
(laughing)
- I could've ended
up like Bob Crane!
- Pa, it won't hurt to try.
- Now, look, honey--
- Please?
- All right, I think about it.
- You know, I'm shrinking at
an alarming rate over here.
- Good morning, boys.
Everything work out
okay last night?
- Did you meet my
brother George?
- Yeah.
- [Cal] I let Pete go.
I don't hold with that
kind of thing in my place.
- [Bix] Yeah.
- I'll be kinda short
of help for a while.
- Hey, he's got a
TV's Frank curl.
- I'll have some
scrambled eggs and coffee.
- And I'll have a penicillin.
- Me too.
- Sure.
- Stop the music,
my eggs are cold!
- What'd he say?
- He said they'll have
scrambled eggs and coffee.
- Ask him, Pa, go on, ask him.
- Would you please go
out with my daughter?
- Nice day.
- For a white wedding.
- Is he comin' on
to us, Big Stupid?
- Psst, don't order the toast.
The toast.
Don't, no.
- You know, their drifting
career has really stalled.
- Be just me and
Carrie now for a while.
Sure could use
somebody to help out.
- I'll be in Vegas next
week with Scott Thorson.
- [Cal] I don't suppose
you'd be interested
in workin' for a spell?
- Me?
I get cold sweats at
the thought of it.
- Why don't you, Bix?
We're getting
kinda low on money.
- We'll manage.
- What about our nest egg?
- We didn't plan
on hangin' around.
- Hey, it's the KMA lady.
- You really stuck?
- Yeah.
- He's got a gull-wing toupee.
- Wormhole!
- Five years later.
- Big, where are the kids?
- I just felt a chill
of horror, honey?
- How about some of those
good powder milk biscuits,
heavens they're tasty.
- What is it with this creep?
He has you shakin'
like a leaf, why?
- I don't like him and
I guess he knows it.
He's always trying to touch me.
- Well you are one of
three women in town.
- I'll wait on him and see
if he'd like to touch me.
- So, you wanna,
hey, don't touch me!
- He looks like a gargoyle.
- What'll you have?
- Antagonist special.
- I want the girl to wait on me.
- She's busy, I'll
take your order.
- I want the girl.
- I said she's busy.
- Well, will you put on a dress
and say, "May I help you?"
- I'll come back when she ain't.
- Man, this new waiter's
just killing their business.
- Ooh, what an odor.
Urine, and brussels
sprouts, maybe?
- You better get ready to
go, I'll take you home.
- Okay.
- Leaving?
- Yep.
It's all yours,
Danny boy, take over.
- Be all by myself in here.
- I'm steppin' into a
pretty big apron here.
- Eric Carmen?
- No you won't.
- Well, enjoy yourself.
- If you get a minute, you might
wait on the customers, too.
- All both of them?
- You got a dime?
- You know, back then, a
dime was like havin' $1,000.
- They're in the
Land of the Lost.
- Watch out for Sleestaks.
- Romance strikes Biosphere Two.
- I like it here on
Omicron Ceti Three, Jim.
- Big, you have a job now,
could we maybe go to
a movie or something?
- I've never been
out of Sherman.
- Well it ain't the world,
there's a lot more than this.
- I guess you've been about
most every place there is.
- Yeah, just about.
- Seen it from the inside
of a boxcar, but just about.
- There, your damn rings.
- Hey, you wanna bath?
- Gee, I've never
had a bath before.
- Oh no, Bix, you wouldn't.
- Come on now, come on.
Come on.
- No!
(laughing)
- I think I broke my
ankle, green stick, too.
(laughing)
- Don't you ever get tired?
I mean, don't you ever
feel like you wanna stop?
- And do what?
- Well, stop and
stay put someplace.
A person's gotta belong
somewhere, doesn't he?
- But nobody doesn't
belong to Sara Lee.
- You see that?
- Boom mike.
Picks up everything we say.
- Had that roof over
my head for so long,
I wouldn't know no other kind.
- Wow, that is so out there.
- You get kinda lonesome
sometimes, don't you, Carrie?
- Yeah, but I just throw
myself at a hobo, and...
- Yeah, I kinda figured that.
- I'll do the talking.
- Don't let it get ya.
Some day, some guy's
gonna come to town
and pick you out
over everybody else.
- Over Millie and
the prostitutes?
- Like you, Bix?
- Sure.
Well, before you know
it, you'll be in love.
- With Super Sugar Crisp.
- That's all you need, to
be in love with some guy.
The right guy.
- Lou!
The right guy Lou.
- How will I know?
♪ If he really loves me ♪
- Beats me, I ain't no expert.
- Well then quit
giving out free advice.
- Well, come on, kid,
you better take me home.
- I can't get my mind off the
rings, really love the rings.
I need the rings.
The rings, the rings...
- Have you ever been in love?
- Well, I liked a cat once.
- No.
Never stayed in one
place long enough.
Never wanted to.
- I'm all screwed-up inside.
- Come on, kid, I'll take
you home, it's gettin' late.
- Would you stop calling
me kid and taking me home?
- Oh, my blouse, it's caught.
- Welp, I gotta go, I'll see ya.
- You mean you can't move?
- No, it's caught on.
- Well, well, well, well, well
this is a very interesting
situation here.
(laughing)
- Well now that
you're half-undressed,
how about that bath now?
- Oh no.
- Big sees her as
half-undressed, I see
her as 90% dressed.
(fun music)
- Is this the way it happens?
- Well, usually there's
dinner and a movie, but yeah.
- Go.
- Big, do you have a sewing kit?
- Oh, it's the stage
manager from Our Town.
- Nice.
- Is she still busy?
Can she wait on me?
- He's actually one of the
better-dressed men in this town.
- The British are coming,
the British are coming.
- Well, here we are,
2615 Lovers Lane.
- I can see pa is home.
- Paw paw paw paw!
Sorry.
- I didn't think he'd
be home this early.
- Where's he been?
- Nick Cumming's son
is getting married,
they had a bachelor
party for him.
- Sounds wild.
- Well.
- If it isn't the great
drifters, king of the hobos.
- Kids have a nice time?
- Yes, Pa.
Looks like you did too.
- Oh, you know me, honey,
I never drink much.
- Now let's see
you drift, drifter.
- Good night, Bix.
- Yeah.
- What, are you mad?
Are you gonna hit me, drifter?
- What's wrong?
- You're drunk.
- Yeah, Mr.
Judgemental over there.
- Took a freight
train from Kansas City
and you're something special?
- You know, Big Stupid is not
a very appealing leading man.
- You know, you got me
there, I'm drunk all right.
I am outta ammo with that one.
- Yeah, I'm gonna go drive,
walk around the front
window in my underwear.
- It's a bloodbath.
- You're drunk too!
- What's up?
- Nothin'.
- Big, I blew my paycheck on
another prostitute, sorry.
- Did you have a
fight with Carrie?
- No.
- You?
- Looks like Blue Boy at
the Dinner Table up there.
- Cal Anders, he was drunk.
- No, not that drunk.
- Smelled like my own man.
- Here it comes.
- Even looked like him.
My old man.
- Think I'll keep him.
- He used to work me over
regular every time he got drunk,
and he got drunk every day.
- So he worked me over
every day, is the point.
- It got to be routine.
- It would, wouldn't it?
- If he didn't slug
me when he came home,
I thought he was sick.
- Was he?
- One night I hit him back.
He fell down and he
never got up again.
He was so full of
booze he drowned in it.
- (laughs) Sorry.
- I killed him.
- My dad missed parents'
night at glee club.
- The doc said the fall
had nothing to do with it--
- So I killed him, too.
- Said his heart just gave out.
- But you said you killed him.
- I did.
- I pulled his heart
out and made it stop.
- I wished him dead.
- So how was your day?
- Once I ate a whole
pack of Sno Balls
and I vomited in the
back seat, it was--
- She's nude!
(gasping)
- Say cheese, everybody.
- Cheese.
- They're losing
their will to drift.
- Eat it all, kids, I made it
with my own two dirty hands.
- I bet you've got a
lot of hidden talent.
- I don't keep nothin'
hidden, it all shows.
(disgusted groaning)
- I want some of that milk.
- What'll you give me for it?
- What do you want?
- If you have to ask,
forget it, tiger.
- Right, here's your dang dime.
(train whistling)
- Can of boop?
- Well, time to drift.
Got driftin' in my
blood, you know.
- What's the matter?
- Nothin', I'll be right back.
- I have to wipe him.
- Your heart's showing.
- I should plug that hole.
- He's leaving
soon, I know he is.
- So?
He leaves and another guy comes
along, what's the problem?
- You go to the doctor,
you get some shots.
- I love him, Peggy.
- Do you?
- It sounds like the
Robbie Douglas band.
- There's no such animal.
- What is she, Lydia
Lunch over here?
- Danny?
- You have a weird body.
- You homesick, kid?
- I guess they're pretty
worried about me by now.
- Ain't hard to
make a phone call,
the operator does all the work.
- No, not yet, I,
I'm not ready yet.
- Well maybe we
oughta be movin' on.
- She's kind of stuck on you.
- Yeah, she's stuck
on another branch.
- Well, maybe you're
stuck on her too.
- Now look, bright boy,
you start playing cupid,
I'm gonna throw you to the fish.
- Bluegills scare me.
- We don't have to move on,
we could stay here for a while.
- No, we'll leave at
the end of the week,
just like we planned.
- Whoa, just cut my
thumb off, oh geez.
- We've been here
too long already.
- Man, I don't know
what the problem is,
maybe the three-bean salad.
- Throw sand on it, gee.
- Hey, you two,
how about a swim?
- Oh, not yet, tiger,
you just finished eating.
- We'll take a walk
with you, though.
- All righty.
- Coming?
- How to stuff a weird bikini.
- That was my favorite scene.
- Here, smell this, will ya?
- Seeing Carrie tonight?
- No, you take tonight off.
- Get yourself rolled.
- But I thought that--
- Don't.
Every time you think,
it gives me a headache.
- Seems to me you
oughta tell her, then.
- He should get a funnel.
- She's not like other girls,
you oughta tell her
we're leaving soon.
- Most girls you can just use.
- I'll be in the back, I
have some supplies to unpack.
- Yeah, my heart-breaking
tools came in.
- (hums) I got a customer!
What do I do, what do I do?
Stay calm, stay calm.
- Pervert burger.
- You by yourself, kid?
- Yeah.
- Where's the girl?
Carrie?
- She--
- Think, man!
- She left early tonight.
- She entered the witness
protection program.
- I was kinda wondering when you
and your partner
are gonna leave.
You know, in this town, we
don't like people who come in
and takin' things
that ain't theirs.
- Call us persnickety.
- You know what I mean?
- Let me get you
some Mexi-skins.
- Hi.
- Bye.
- Ammonia, grass clippings,
what is that odor?
- What is it with this creep?
Every time he shows up,
somebody gets the jitters.
- I don't know, there's
something about him, his eyes.
- His overpowering stench.
- He's not the harmless
idiot they think he is.
- I am.
- What'd he want?
- Carrie.
- This is like a
Route 66 episode.
- I'll take tonight
off after all, okay?
- Sure.
I'd hate to meet him in
a dark alley some night.
- What would you do, run?
- Oh, that hurt, why
can't you ever support me?
- I got a hankerin' to
humiliate a drunk dad.
- Bix.
- Oh, hi.
Has Foster Brooks
stumbled out of bed yet?
- Hi.
Where are you going?
- Got a lot on my mind, I
thought I'd take a walk.
- Hey, will you show me
the thing with the egg
and the pop bottle again?
- Sure.
- Come on.
- That would be nice.
- Okay now, Tom,
I don't want you
doing this on your own, okay?
- Okay, now, egg-xactly what's
gonna happen again? (laughs)
- Well, what happens is
the fire burns up all
the oxygen in the bottle
and creates a vacuum--
- Oh, and then the egg gets
sucked down into the bottle,
cool, what a neat experiment.
- I'm Jack Elam. (groans)
- What you got here?
- It says here in
the Webelos Handbook
that it should take about
two or three minutes,
oh look, it's Jack Elam.
- Place egg on top of, oh, hi,
nice Jack Elam costume, Crow.
It will slip in the bottle, huh.
So, has it done it yet?
- No.
- Here are the
goods you ordered.
- No no, don't bump
the desk, the egg!
- Don't talk to me, I only
want to deal with Gypsy,
she around?
- Crow, we get that you're
dressed like Jack Elam, okay?
- Not just dressed like,
am Elam, am Jack Elam!
To live like the Elam--
- The egg's moving!
- It is?
- Uh, no, I guess not.
- Look, look, look at me,
look at me a sec, look, look,
look, I'll do that
bouncy thing he does.
You guys are a tough crowd.
I worked a long time on this.
- It's great Crow, you
really look like him.
- Yeah, Crow, but maybe you look
a little too much
like Jack Elam, hm?
- Yeah, well maybe I do, Servo,
what's wrong with that, huh?
Jack Elam was a brilliant
character actor,
for all I know he still is.
And you know what?
I've never been as Jack
Elam as I am at this moment.
I am Jack Elam, and I
don't need your pity.
- Yes, you do.
- What are you saying,
that I'm a total failure?
- No, I'm saying that
you're a total failure
and you look like Jack Elam.
- You guys don't appreciate me.
- Come on, let's go,
we got commercial sign
and we gotta get a
new egg, all right.
- Pardon me, Crow, excuse me.
(screaming)
- [Crow] I'm not
Jack Elam anymore.
(fun music)
- I dunno, maybe
a soft-boiled egg.
- Did I say something or--
- Sorry, guys.
- Do something you didn't like?
- You're drunk, aren't ya?
- Look, Carrie.
- You're so very.
- I don't know how to take you.
- You say you're gonna
wear a yellow dress.
- I don't know what
to do with you.
I'm a drifter, a nobody.
I ain't the guy you've
been waitin' for.
- You ate him? Why?
- I don't wanna hurt you.
- I like you, Dotty, like!
- I'm no good for you, Carrie.
- But I've never
met anyone like you.
- And if you're lucky,
you never will again.
You don't know anything.
- Thanks, I think.
- [Bix] Now's the time for you
to learn all the nice things.
I can't teach 'em to ya.
- I'm booked solid!
- Things you'd learn from me
you'd be better
off never knowin'.
- Like algebra.
- Ask your old man, he's
got me pegged right.
He knows I don't stay put.
- I think he'd like you to stay.
- He said, "I'd
like him to stay."
- Inside of a week he'd
be pushin' me around,
slappin' me down.
- Sellin' me to
foreign dignitaries.
- Makin' me hit back.
- Aw, heck, I'll stay.
- It's no good, you and me,
Carrie, it's just no good.
- Love should be musky
and whiskery and bad.
- [Bix] Go on.
- Before--
- They're time traveling
again, stop it!
- If I'm something new to you--
- Something nudie?
- Then maybe I could
teach you something, too.
- How to crinkle-cut fries?
- Good night, Carrie.
- You're so very.
(exciting music)
- How do you like
my theme music?
- Big Stupid did a great
job protectin' her.
- Jack, no, drop her, drop her.
- Well if ain't
little Carrie Anders,
Miss Innocence herself.
And you can stop play actin',
because I followed you
and your love here.
- Stay away from me, Jesse.
- He's taken on a Torgo quality.
- Very Torgo-esque.
- He don't stay away from ya.
And all I want is
just to kiss ya.
- No, no.
- Hey!
- Jack, stop it!
- Knock it off!
Don't you--
- Boo!
- Touchin' don't hurt none,
and you can stop pretending
you're so lily white,
didn't I tell ya I was
watchin' you and him?
- Stop, stop!
No, no!
- Okay, good night, Carrie.
(screaming)
♪ Big Stupid to the rescue ♪
- My Big Stupid!
- Stop it!
(cheering)
- There we go.
Down he goes.
- Why did I want to be him?
- Hey, my eye went
straight, thanks.
- Just tryin' to kiss her.
She always says,
"No, no, Jesse."
- Now, Jack has a
legitimate beef there.
- Some day you ain't
gonna be around.
- To pick up the pieces when
somebody breaks your heart.
- Well, I'm gonna
leave you again,
he probably won't be
back, you'll be fine.
- Let's go make some
of your dumb rings.
- What time will
you be over tonight?
- I don't know, I have to check
with Danny about something.
- I'm right here.
- The time's run out,
that's it, isn't it, Bix?
- You better go on home,
Danny and I'll finish up here.
- Yeah, finish up here.
- But I ordered a tuna melt!
- I've, I have a
surprise for you,
something I wanna show you.
- I got you that new seven iron.
- I'll see you
later, later tonight.
- Are you ever gonna
not shoo me away?
- I counted, we have
87 straws, Big, 87.
- Does she know?
- How should I know?
Maybe she does,
maybe she doesn't.
- Good point.
- Look, Bix, I told you we
could stay here for a while.
At least until you're ready to--
- I'm ready now, man.
- Hey, he called me man!
- Are you sure you're
doing the right thing?
- Now ain't this great,
you givin' me advice.
- I'm only trying to help.
- Well when I need your
help, you little punk,
I'll whistle for ya.
- What's the matter with you?
- Whistler's Mother.
- [Bix] All of a sudden,
everybody knows what's
good for Bix, even you.
Well look at you, you can't
solve your own problems,
but you got mine
all figured out.
- I don't get it.
- Well who's askin' ya to?
- Third base!
- Who's askin' for any of this?
Look, I don't need you, Danny
boy, and I don't need her.
- Don't say me, don't say me.
- I've never been tied down
before and I'm not
gonna start now.
So get off my back, will you?
Go on, get outta here.
- We're out of
French onion soup.
- I said get outta here!
- Don't you look
at me like that,
go lay down outside,
go lay down.
- Bill Coontz said he'd
give us a lift outta town.
The truck pulls out at 10 sharp.
- That's great, you be on it.
- Oh, one last thing, could
you work for me Monday?
- Oh.
- Men!
(humming romantic music)
(humming fun music)
(humming dramatic music)
(humming exciting music)
- That's Barnaby Jones.
- Well, yeah.
Oh, sorry.
- You know, she's
so well-trained, she
never leaves the yard
and does all her business
in one little section.
- So very.
- Bix.
I was beginning
to think that you,
I had the funniest feeling.
- It seems to me
that you were...
- I can't explain anything.
- I was just about to eat a...
- There's only a
half a pound of...
- It's true then, isn't it?
- You're a Nazi.
- You came to say goodbye.
- Well, you made
it easy, see ya!
♪ Oh for the open road ♪
- Carrie, I gotta
make you understand,
I don't know what I want.
Maybe you're it,
I just don't know.
- Please, just yes or no.
Are you leaving tonight?
♪ Are you leaving tonight ♪
♪ Should I come back again ♪
- Carrie, listen, I'll be back.
But I will, I need
time, I have to think.
- I have to go through
a visioning process.
- I've tried to give you
a reason for staying,
but you wouldn't let me.
- Come on, kid, I'll
take ya home, oh.
- All my life I never
belonged to nobody.
- Anybody.
- I learned to live with it.
I even learned to like it.
- How nice for you.
- Look, try to
understand, Carrie,
I didn't want this, I
didn't want to get close,
it just happened.
And I ain't sure if it's for me.
- Aren't sure.
- She's gonna blow!
- Maybe I gotta learn what
it is to, to need someone.
- You're stepping on
the ball of my foot.
- Carrie...
- You're so very.
- So, Danny tells me
you killed your dad.
- I gotta take
Danny's sitter home.
- I'm going back to
the Enterprise, Carrie.
- Oh, yeah, that reminds me,
when can I get my last paycheck?
Oh, I'll catch ya later.
- Tryin' to make these
buildings explode as I walk by,
but it's not workin'.
♪ Memories, like the
corners of my mind ♪
- This is where he used to say,
"I'd better take you home, kid."
♪ Sad young girl
from Lovers Lane ♪
- My battalion's
movin' out soon.
- Gene Kelly!
- I can't wait any
longer, I'm late now.
♪ Gotta dance, gotta dance ♪
(crying)
- Somethin's botherin' her.
- This is where we
used to eat dirt.
(exciting music)
- This man could win $5,000!
(fun music)
(pastoral music)
Hey, if you're drunk, it's okay.
- Shovel your walk?
Oh, it's summer, that's right.
- Well, I'll see
if she's out here,
maybe I can call her
kid and take her home.
♪ Girl in Lovers Lane ♪
Look, a buffalo-head nickel!
- Carrie!
- Have you seen my keys?
- Carrie, who did it?
- And do you have someone to
cover your shift tomorrow?
- My dress, it
has ruffles on it.
- Those ruffles have ridges.
- Hold on, I'm still
talking about my dress.
- I love you.
(screaming)
- Ah, Edvard Munch is here.
- What was that?
- I don't know, I just
arrived in this film.
- I'll go find out.
- No, don't go.
- Look, you stay right here.
- But your pants!
- Oh, Carrie.
- So very.
- Forgive me.
- For I have sinned
and it's been three weeks
since my last confession.
- Carrie, you were right,
a guy does have to
belong to somebody.
- I belong to William Conrad.
- Carrie, oh Carrie.
Carrie.
- Oh, sorry,
didn't know you were
posin' for a romance novel.
- We drove onto a movie
set, let's get outta here.
- What was it?
- We've gotta go
get the sheriff.
- The cafe heiress
has been killed!
- She died.
- And she was so very.
- In my arms.
- You've told me that.
- Man, they're really
packin' in the new characters
at the end of this movie.
♪ This is the night the lights
went out in wherever they are ♪
- What a night.
♪ Late September, back in '63 ♪
- This has been a peaceful
town for 20 years.
There's gonna be trouble,
can't you understand that?
- Please, I'm brooding.
- I loved her.
I never got a
chance to tell her.
- She has to order
more frying medium.
- She cried.
Can you beat that?
A beautiful thing like her,
cryin' over a slob like me?
- Listen to me.
- You're stuck here!
- [Sheriff] Have you
ever seen a lynch mob?
- Uh, in a play once.
- And what do you think that
silence means out there?
That everyone's asleep?
- Listen, when you
kill in this town,
you get a stern lecture
from the sheriff.
- By morning, that
silence will be
the loudest noise
you've ever heard.
- Oh, well, huh?
- She died so easy.
- Like she'd done it before.
- It didn't take much.
- All you had to
do was murder her.
- Now I'm gonna be late for
the James Drury convention.
- The dress, it, it
had ruffles on it.
- And ridges, son?
- She was wearing the yellow
dress, I didn't even notice!
- Until I tried it on.
- We can and will hold
this against you, son,
although it's weird.
- All right now, show's over.
- Well, I checked that
whole area up there.
- Who's?
- Couldn't find a thing.
He tell ya anything?
- I can't reach him.
You'd better put him in a cell.
- I'm gonna go home
and watch Dorf on Golf.
- Come on, boy.
- You want the
fanti-cell tonight?
- And then we'll
have to load these.
- And I don't envy you that job.
- Genuine Mausers, got
'em from the Kaiser.
- It's been a long time
since we've had to use 'em.
- Boy, he's just really
peeved about this murder.
- What do you say, Mac?
- Hi, Bill.
- Gotta dance, Jack.
- How about checkin'
this right front tire,
it feels kind of low.
- Sure.
- Feelin' mighty low.
- Well I guess
Sherman's really buzzin'
with excitement, huh?
- Sherman Hemsley,
he's gonna do The
Jeffersons live.
- Murder, in a town that size.
- What are you talkin' about?
- Will, didn't
you hear about it?
- You got your head up your--
- Yeah, my brother-in-law
phoned a couple of hours ago
and said some girl by the
name of Anders was killed.
- Saw it on Matlock.
- Carrie Anders.
- Carrie?
- Yeah, did you know her?
- She was my friend's girl.
- Well don't worry, they
got the punk who did it.
Some stranger.
They oughta hang the bum.
- Phil, you gotta take me back.
- Now look, you know I've--
- $20.
- I've gotta run--
- 30!
- Sold, American!
- Tire okay?
- Yeah, it's okay.
- Well, I do gotta dance.
- Relax, kid,
you're on your way.
- Well, Danny sure can
charm the older set.
- Oh, I'm just so beat
from loadin' all them guns.
- Hold it, hold it right there.
- What are you gonna do?
- Bring him out.
- Panty raid.
- Bring him out
here now, Charles.
- Don't do this, Cal, you don't
know that he killed Carrie.
But what you're doin' is murder!
- Gimme the keys.
- Listen to me.
- No, you listen to me!
- He's drunk again.
- Are you gonna
bring him out here
or do I have to
go get him myself?
- I lost my best waitress.
- Jim, come out here.
- Should I draw my, oh.
- Put him in a cell.
Put 'em both in a cell.
- If you can't afford a lawyer,
the court will
appoint one for you.
- Think what you're doin'.
Commander.
- I'm sorry I called you
a drunk a while back.
- What is this?
- I'm gonna beat you, boy.
Beat you 'til you
can't stand up,
and turn you over to the others.
- Hey, that sounds, oh.
- Hey, you gotta
believe me, I wouldn't--
- Get him outta there.
- They took turns at Big Stupid,
and there was three of them.
- Where's my daily platter?
Gotta leave a note for myself.
- We got 'em, we
got 'em, we got 'em.
- Yeah, we got 'em here!
(cheering)
- Whoa, they're takin'
him way outta town.
- We got 'em, we
got 'em, we got 'em.
- Can't you go any faster?
- We're doin' the limit now.
- And I got one of them
bumper stickers that says,
"If you don't like
my driving, well..."
- Kill him.
- I wouldn't hurt
her, I loved her!
- You loved her?!
- That's great!
- She tied you down,
that's what you said,
I heard you myself.
- No, no.
- Carrie's dad really
shines in a crisis.
- Why did you do it, my
beautiful little girl?
I knew you were no good.
- Gollum, Gollum.
- [Cal] Why don't you hit back?
- Hey, that guy's taking
credit for my murder.
- [Cal] You dirty, lousy--
- Hey, anybody sittin' here?
- Fight back, you coward!
- Can I squeeze in here?
Thanks.
- You dirty punk, why,
why did you do it?
(laughing)
- Actually it's really more
ironic than funny, isn't it?
- [Cal] I knew you were no good.
- You know, that truck looks
like an English Bulldog.
(barking)
- [Cal] Get him, get him!
You stinking coward.
Fight!
- Back off, wormy.
- What are you doing?
- Ooh, good wood on that one.
- Lemme through.
I said let me through!
- Please let me
through, I'm a hobo!
- Get up, get up!
- You're fired!
- [Cal] Come on, get him up.
- Think they'll get him up?
- Get up and fight!
- You think I killed
your daughter, oh.
- Looks like Jack's
doin' an open stage.
- Jesse.
- Now Jerome.
- Gotta go get them pot
stickers outta the wok.
- I'm tryin' to look at nobody
and I'm lookin' at everybody!
- Isn't that the trail
boss from Wagon Train?
- [Cal] Get up and fight!
- That sequence is
over, let's get him!
- He's at the 20, good
open field tackle.
- Don't pass out on me now.
- Not yet, no no no no,
don't pass out on me now.
- Get up.
- He's wrong.
I didn't touch her,
I didn't touch her.
- I'll bet you didn't.
- Hey, look what I found,
it's a Danny O'Day dummy.
- Now you get over there
and tell them what you did.
- I didn't touch her.
I didn't mean to kill her.
- (laughs) Nobody can say
they coerced it out of him.
- She was tryin' to scream,
I didn't mean to kill her.
- Well I didn't mean
to kill her so much.
♪ Gotta dance ♪
- Well, you had to be there.
♪ S'wonderful, s'marvelous ♪
- The keys are in
the other door.
♪ Moses supposes his
toeses are roses ♪
♪ Moses supposes erroneously ♪
- Hey, don't you want your
$20 and your new suit?
(humming fun music)
- Quick, move his head, he
may have a spinal injury.
- If I aim it just right, there.
(somber music)
- We gotta get some
more women in this town.
- Big, how 'bout a burger
with all the trimmings?
- He's the one.
You made a mistake.
(growling)
- Hey, somebody wanna grab Jack?
- That's probably a good idea.
- This came in a
couple of days ago.
I didn't know we had
a celebrity in town.
- You're Scott Thorson.
- There's the phone, boy.
- Can I hit you just once?
Never got a chance to,
I was locked up in here.
- He should sue him.
'Cause even if it was just $100,
back in those days--
- Yeah.
- He was wrong,
he'll pay for it.
- Carrie's dead.
- And you almost were.
- [Danny] Long distance, please.
I'd like to make a collect call
to Mr. or Mrs. John
Winslow in Larchmont.
- Tell Danny I'll be back.
- He'll be back.
- Dad?
(imitates dialtone)
It's great to hear
your voice, too.
- Hopped a freight, met a guy,
he got beat up, I got
beat up, he met a girl.
- That's swell, dad.
- You're gonna kill
the fatted calf?
- Well look, it's too
long to go into now,
but I'm bringing someone
home with me, a friend.
- Oh, and he killed his dad,
so don't bring that up, okay?
- Oh, Siddhartha.
- Black gold, Texas tea.
- [Carrie] I love
the rings they make
when they hit the water.
- Yeah, well there you go.
- [Carrie] Have you
ever been in love?
- Well I was, but she died.
- Golly, I'm stupid,
I'm dumber than an
eight-pound hammer, I am.
- Bix.
Bix?
- You know, I'd like to see you
in a yellow dress with ruffles.
- We're goin' home.
- Come to daddy.
- And so, Bix and Danny
left the clam flow--
- Cut it out, stop it.
- Oh, sorry.
That was one weird-ass movie.
- See the further
adventures of Danny and Bix,
this fall on NBC!
Joel, Tom and I have
been horribly scarred
by the way this movie ended,
and that means we're
filled with rage.
(growling)
- Whoa, just back off
you guys, you know,
you can write a different
ending if you want.
(grunting)
Yeah, it's just fiction, I mean,
you don't have to accept
the ending they hand you.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
- Oh, okay, oh,
just a minor change.
What would happen if the
nice restaurant woman lived?
- You think it even
occurred to 'em?
- And instead Jack Elam is--
- Gone.
- Right, and then Big
Stupid and Danny get a grant
and they renovate the cafe.
A real Chili's feel without
all the Chili's crap.
You know, a fun place
for a birthday, Joel.
Free hats, prize buckets,
you know, hoopdy doody...
- How's this, Jack Elam
is kidnapped by aliens.
- Mean aliens.
- Sure, mean aliens.
Then Big Stupid and his
little pal leave that town,
'cause they're driftwood, and
then the apocalypse happens,
and dinosaurs roam the land,
and they capture dinosaurs
and they tame them,
and they ride 'em like horses
and we see the bond
between man and lizard,
et cetera, et cetera,
and it goes on and on.
- Crow, aren't you getting a
little bit away from the movie?
- Bear with me.
Then, there are pygmies.
- Oh, yeah!
- Yeah, who live in
a vast pygmy kingdom.
- Okay, let's read a couple
of letters here, okay?
This one's from Steve
Boinko of Uniontown, Ohio.
Please put that on Still-Store.
- Oh, the pygmies have lain
hidden throughout the eons,
and they are wise
and they disdain you
with your stinking machines.
- Stinking machines,
they'll stink you up.
- Okay, and he says, "My
sister thinks Servo is so cute,
"what is Gypsy's last name?"
And--
- Oh, I got it.
The pygmies are poison if you
touch 'em, so don't touch 'em.
- Okay.
- Everything's at stake.
- And for the
Invention Exchange,
you should have a garbage
disposal trash can.
So that's from Steve--
- And they can tell
when you're thinkin'
bad thoughts about 'em,
so don't even think about it.
- You see, 'cause if
you think about...
- Okay, and this one
is from Susie Belts
of Rochester, New York,
she sent a picture,
put that on Still--
- Oh, oh oh oh, oh oh oh!
- Okay, okay, what?
- Then you fall in
a love with a pygmy.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, yeah.
I love that, 'cause it--
- Yeah, love it.
- [Joel] Okay, and
then she writes,
"I like the time when you sang
Master Ninja Theme Song--"
- And the moral, you see,
is never love a pygmy.
- Because they're immortal.
And they can fly,
and you can't fly!
- So you see, your heart's
naturally gonna be broken.
- Okay, and then she writes,
"I like your show so much
"I give it 100 plus
100 equals 200."
- You see what happens is
then, the pygmies get a bus
and they drive all
the way to Hollywood!
- Florida.
- Florida, yeah!
'Cause they're comin'
from Hollywood.
- And this is from Rebecca
of Appleton, Wisconsin,
and she writes, "Dear
Joel, Gypsy, Tom--"
- You see, 'cause Peter Lawford
and Peter Lorre are with,
were in this film with
them in Hollywood?
And then their heads
started exploding
when they went across the desert
and were headed towards Florida,
because, wait, we
gotta work on this.
- And how come Crow always
gets time outs for being sassy?
I think Joel--
- I like it!
- Ivan Reitman could direct.
- Peter Lawford and Peter Lorre
could be called Pete and Repeat!
That would be, 'cause it's--
- We get Ivan Reitman.
- Joel is a little
hard on 'em anyway,
I think Joel should get
a time out for once,
what do you think?
- And then they
head for the stars.
And then you learn
some kind of lesson,
and then you go home.
- Now that's a better ending.
- What do you think, sirs?
- No, Frank, no more
alternate endings.
- No, wait, hear me out on this.
Now, I envision Big
Stupid as pure energy.
- Pure energy?
- Yes, but--
- I'm fascinated, Frank.
Step this way.
- He's plucky pure energy.
- Plucky pure.
- Pure energy with a heart.
- Just have a seat.
Lay down there
and, if you would,
hold this railroad
spike on your skull?
- [Frank] Sure, now I
envision a moment of truth.
Now there could be lots
of adventurous scenes--
- Here's a moment of truth.
- With him confront--
- Well--
- [Frank] I also see a role
for Charles Durning in this,
there could be--
- 'Til next time, Joel.
- [Frank] Then there
could be another scene--
("Mighty Science
Theater" by Joel Hodgson)
- Are you waiting for a bus?